RG 002:025, Government Administration and Elections Committee
Connecticut State Library
Government Administration and Elections Committee records
1978-2006
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. General Assembly. Government Administration and Elections Committee
4.5 cubic feet
Government Administration and Elections Committee meeting and investigation files.
RG002_025_GAE
Multiple
Scope and Content
Accessions T001597, T003071, 1998-012, 1999-157, 2001-055 contain mostly meeting minutes and agendas, membership lists, and lists of bills.
Accession 2009-020 contains the investigation files in the matter of whether M. Lisa Moody violated state election laws in relation to a fundraising event for Gov. Rell's campaign.
Arrangement
Arranged by accession.
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. General Assembly. Government Administration and Elections Committee
Subjects:
Connecticut. General Assembly. Government Administration and Elections Committee -- Records and correspondence; Elections -- Corrupt practices; Legislative hearings -- Connecticut; Misconduct in office -- Connecticut; Political campaigns -- Connecticut
Document Types:
Agendas; Correspondence; Membership lists; Minutes; Reports; Transcripts
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Accession T001597, 1984-1988
  - Meeting minutes, Election Sub-committee, 1983 February 16, March 10, 22 (Box 1)
  - Meeting minutes and agenda, 1984 March 15 (Box 1)
  - List of bills, 1984 (Box 1)
    Includes Joint Favorable report.
  - Meeting minutes and agenda, 1985 February 25 (Box 1)
  - Meeting minutes and agendas, 1986 January 30, March 24, 26, May 2 (Box 1)
    Includes vote tally sheet and copies of bills.
  - Public hearing agendas, 1986 February 14, 18 (Box 1)
  - List of bills, 1986 (Box 1)
    Includes Joint Favorable Report and Attendance Summary.
  - Sale of old New Britain Armory as State surplus property, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Meeting minutes, 1987 October 20 (Box 1)
  - Membership, 1987 (Box 1)
  - General Assembly membership and committee assignments, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Meeting minutes and agendas, 1988 January 28, February 1, 3, 14, March 25, 28, April 7 (Box 1)
    Includes copies of some bills.
  - Subcommittee on Freedom of Information Recodification meeting minutes plus draft report to the General Assembly, 1988 January 15 (Box 1)
  - Subcommittee on Campaign Ethics meeting minutes, 1988 January 20 (Box 1)
  - Membership schedules, 1988 (Box 1)
  - List of bills with Joint Favorable report, 1988 (Box 1)
- Accession T003071, 1979-1993
  - Meeting minutes, agendas, correspondence and public hearings, 1979-1993 (Box 4-6)
- Accession 1998-012, 1989, 1996
  - Meeting minutes and agendas, 1989 January 11, 20, 30, February 3, 10, 14, 17, 24, March 3, 8, 17, 27, 31, April 3, 7, 10, 18, 26, May 4 (Box 1)
  - Meeting minutes and agendas, 1996 March 4 (Box 1)
- Accession 1999-157, 1990, 1995; 3 folders
  - Attendance sheets, 1990 (Box Shared box)
  - Bill book, 1995 (Box Shared box)
  - Bill status book, 1995 (Box Shared box)
- Accession 2001-055, 1978-1996; 2 folders
  - Correspondence, 1978-1984 (Box Shared box)
    Includes report, "Party Democracy: Reforming the Nominating Procedure", 1979.
  - Meeting minutes and agendas, 1989-1996 (Box Shared box)
  - Bill status book, 1995 (Box 1)
- Accession 2009-020, 2005-2006
  - Gov. M. Jodi Rell campain fundraising event investigation files, 2005-2006
    Investigation into fundraising event for Gov. Rell's campaign held on December 7, 2005 at the Marco Polo Restaurant in East Hartford.
    - Investigation report, 2006 January 31 (Box 1)
    - Correspondence, 2006 April - September (Box 1)
    - News clippings, 2006 May - July (Box 1)
    - Rules and procedures for GAE hearings on election law enforcement (Box 1)
    - May 10, 2006 (Box 1)
      This folder contains documents related to requesting individuals to testify at a public hearing.
    - Public hearing transcripts, 2006 (Box 1)
      - Chirstopher Morano, 2006 March 8 (Box 1)
        Morano was the Chief State's Attorney.
      - Luigi G. Vasquez, 2006 May 10 (Box 1)
        Vasquez was Treasurer of the Rell '06 campaign.
      - Peggy Deschenes and Daniel Moreland, 2006 May 11 (Box 1)
        Deschenes was Finance Director of the Rell '06 campaign.
        Moreland was Executive Aide to M. Lisa Moody.
      - Linda Yelmini and Brian Mattiello, 2006 May 12 (Box 1)
        Yelmini was Commissioner of the Dept. of Administrative Services.
        Mattiello was Chief of Staff at the Dept. of Children and Families.
      - Michael Starkowski and Kevin Deneen, 2006 May 15 (Box 1)
        Starkowski was the Deputy Commissioner at the Dept. of Social Services.
        Deneen was Campaign Manager of the Rell '06 campaign.
      - M. Lisa Moody, 2006 May 16 (Box 1)
        Moody was Chief of Staff to Gov. Rell.
      - Rachel Rubin, 2006 May 18 (Box 1)
        Rubin was Special Counsel for Ethics Compliance.
      - Jeffrey B. Garfield, 2006 May 19 (Box 1)
        Garfield was Executive Director of the State Election Enforcement Commission.
    - Records and documents, 2005-2006 (Box 1)
      Documents related to the investigation received from various individuals.
      - Investigation report, 2006 January 31 (Box 1)
      - Joan M. Andrews (Box 1)
      - Marc W. Crayton, 2 folders (Box 1)
      - Kevin Deneen, 2 folders (Box 1)
      - Peggy Deschenes (Box 1)
      - Jeffrey B. Garfield (Box 1)
      - Jeffrey B. Garfield (Box 2)
      - Stephen E. Korta, 2 folders (Box 2)
      - Lisa Moody (Box 2)
      - Daniel Moreland (Box 2)
      - Michael Starkowski (Box 2)
      - Linda Yelmini (Box 2)
      - (1)(a), SEEC original production, Bates 0000001 to 001363, 2006 April 25 (Box 2)
      - (1)(b) continued, SEEC original production, Bates 0000001 to 001363, 2006 April 25 (Box 2)
      - (2), SEEC supplemental production, Bates 001364 to 001644, 2006 May 15 (Box 2)
      - (3), SEEC production, Bates 001645 to 002064, 2006 July 12 (Box 2)
      - Restricted (Box Item 3)
        Campaign contribution forms and check images that contain personal financial information. Redacted copies are found in the Kevin Deneen file.
    - Rep. Demetrios Giannaros papers (Box 2)
      Papers from Rep. Demetrios Giannaros (D-Farmington) received on December 20, 2010.